same occasion Yes yes it one
chance
Uh what about that relationship Uh
I imagine that
eh because you have told me that you have played
enter what you have done with n 14 days
previously it Have you recorded on your
Alzheimer's disease also appeared M can
so to speak with those factors you can
say something then from forensic medicine
regarding Er how it affects so that
say the assessment of their this one
persons and and this plastic then it
nice, there is reason to assume
then once I uh I went there with my
colleague when Eh the daughter was there so it has
planning didn't know she was home
So we came suddenly so Then she was home
mm Otherwise when when she was at home So we we
have never been there m Then you weren't
there or you were No No then it happened